var questions = [{
    question: 'Who played Chandler\'s father on Friends?',
    answers: [
        'Nathan Lane',
        'Michael Douglas',
        'Kathleen Turner',
        'Elliot Gould'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: 'In Bewitched, what part of her body does Samantha twitch to practice magic?',
    answers: [
        'Her ears',
        'Her botom',
        'Her nose',
        'Her forehead'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: 'Every episode of Seinfeld contains an image or reference to what superhero?',
    answers: [
        'Superman',
        'Plastic man',
        'Batman',
        'Spiderman'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: 'What TV series showed the first interracial kiss on American network television?',
    answers: [
        'All in the Family',
        'Family Feud',
        'The Cosby Show',
        'Star Trek'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: 'What is the phrase on the UFO poster in Fox Mulders office in X-Files?',
    answers: [
        'I want to Belive',
        'The Truth is Out There',
        'Trust No One',
        'We are Not Alone'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: 'What television series was the first to air the sound of a toilet being flushed?',
    answers: [
        'The Addams Family',
        'Leave it to Beaver',
        'Maude',
        'All in the Family'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3
}, {
    question: 'Who shot J.R.?',
    answers: [
        'Sue Ellen Ewing',
        'Pamela Barnes Ewing',
        'Kristin Shepard',
        'Jenna Wade'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: 'What color was Jeannie\'s harem costume in I Dream of Jeannie?',
    answers: [
        'Pink',
        'Blue',
        'Green',
        'Yellow'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0
}, {
    question: 'In what TV show did Sheriff Andy Taylor first appear?',
    answers: [
        'Gomer Pyle: USMC',
        'Mayberry R.F.D.',
        'The Danny Thomas Show',
        'The Andy Griffith Show'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2
}, {
    question: 'What sort of business did George Jefferson own on The Jeffersons?',
    answers: [
        'Butcher shop',
        'Dry cleaner',
        'Construction company',
        'Gas station'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1
}];